♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
—·@Phuckq 译制·—
好了 姑娘们 听好了
Okay, ladies, listen up.
本月是"敏捷特训月" 我希望同学们
Since it's "Focus on Agility" month, for the rest of the class,
可以多多练习侧手翻 劈叉和空中技巧
I want you all to work on your cartwheels, splits and aerials.
Brittany 这个劈叉真漂亮
Brittany, that's a perfect split.
谢谢夸奖 Morris老师
Thanks, Ms. Morris.
真是有意思 所有"敏捷特训月"的动作
Funny how all the drills for "Focus on Agility" month are the same ones
在翘掉啦啦操训练溜去正常体育课的时候都用得到
you'd do if you were trying to sneak a cheerleader practice into regular gym class.
没错 而且我不打算妥协
Yes, and I don't intend to stand for it.
想让我做俯卧蹲跳
They can have my squat-thrusts
先撬开我冰冷僵硬的手指再说
when they pry them from my cold, dead hands.
啥?
What?
没什么
I don't know.
你是看上谁了还是随便瞅瞅啊?
See something you like or just browsing?
我是想买他那双跑鞋
I'm thinking about getting those running shoes.
是嘛 鞋什么颜色的?
Uh-huh. What color were they?
拜托不要再窥探人家的内心了 好吧?
Just kick the bleachers out from underneath me, okay?
呃噢 被抓到了
Uh-oh, busted.
姑娘们
Ladies.
你们为什么不跟其他同学一起训练
Why aren't you exercising with the rest of the class?
我们在训练啊
We are exercising.
我们在训练拒绝练操的权利
We're exercising our right to abstain from cheerleader practice.
这不是啦啦操 这是敏捷练习
That's not cheerleading, it's agility.
Jane Lane 你就是跟你姐姐一个德性
Jane Lane, you're just like your sisters, aren't you?
我们有相同的染色体对
We share certain chromosome pairs.
除此之外 我就不能再说了
Beyond that, I'm not supposed to say.
你们明明懂我意思
You know what I mean.
成不了集体中的一员 永远都要特立独行
Can't be part of a group. Always have to be different.
你姐姐Penny也从来没想着要配合
Your sister Penny never wanted to participate, either.
我教了她一点美国人的竞争意识
I taught her a thing or two about the American competitive spirit.
当然喽
You sure did.
难怪她过去十年都没回国
That's why she's spent the last ten years out of the country.
我知道她都受的什么教育
I know what kind of upbringing she's had.
你又有什么借口
What's your excuse?
我只是单纯水平差
I'm just plain no good?
人生就是个大笑话对吧
Life's just one big joke, isn't it?
那我就是要来让你们接受现实世界的
Well, I'm here to prepare you for the real world.
你们俩放了学来见我 把这节课补上
I'll see you both after school to make up this class.
谁来救救我啊 拜托
Can somebody help me, please?
哎哟 你怎么看上去一脸衰相啊 Mack老爹
Yo, how come you look so down, Mack Daddy?
别这么叫我
Don't call me that.
我今天伦理学考砸了
I think I screwed up that ethics test today.
你怎么样
How'd you do?
好得不得了
Pretty good.
等等 你根本没在
Wait a minute. You weren't even there today.
期中考试你还翘课
You cut class on the day of a midterm?
我不用考 他们同意了
I was excused. I didn't have to take the test.
教练跟老师说过了
Coach talked to the teacher, and I got by.
你是说你免考了?
You mean you got "a bye."
没错
Yeah, that's it.
教练说我要留在队里 成绩得保持在C的水平
Coach says I gotta maintain a "C" average to stay on the team,
所以他就帮我关照了一下
so he took care of it or something.
诶 这不公平
Hey, that's not fair.
我也在队里 为什么我要学习
I'm on the team and I had to study.
我是四分卫啊 Mack老爹
I'm the Q.B., Mack Daddy.
我跟你说过一百万遍了 不要这么叫我
I've told you a million times, don't call me that!
你这个榆木脑袋什么时候才听得进去
When are you going to get it through your thick skull already?
如果你不高兴就该说出来嘛 哥们
If that's how you feel all you had to do was say so, bro.
哥们啊 怎么啦 哥们
So, bro... what's wrong, bro?
你听见了吗
Did you hear that?
是谁说人生很公平来着
Whoever said life was fair?
我不知道 但是我肯定他是个四分卫
I don't know, but I'll bet he was a quarterback.
你知道吗 我做了个焦虑的怪梦
You know, I had this weird anxiety dream
数学课随堂测验
where we had this pop quiz in math
我完全没准备
that I was totally unprepared for.
你穿着内衣吗
Were you in your underwear?
没有 所以我才发现不是做梦
No. That's how I figured out it wasn't a dream.
呃噢 成绩不理想吗
Uh-oh. Not a great score on the quiz?
我在数学上的全C战绩很有滑落到D的危险
My straight "C" average in math is now in serious danger of becoming a "D."
所以我要去自习室了
So I'm off to study hall.
去补觉吗
To finish your nap?
你太懂我了
You know me too well.
哟 哥们 咋了
Yo, bro, what's wrong?
我在这陪着你呢 哥们
I'm here for you, bro.
喂 哥们 等我啊
Hey, bro, wait up!
咦 Daria 你今天怎么这么晚回家
Gee, Daria, you're home late from school today.
Quinn永远都这么晚回家
Quinn's always home this late.
是啊 不过那是因为她总是和一些...
Yeah, but that's because she's usually with some...
我的天哪 Daria 你跟男生约会去啦
oh, my gosh, Daria, you met a guy!
事实上 我回来晚是因为要补体育课
Actually, I'm late because I had to make up gym class.
你跟你老爸还假装什么呀
Oh, you don't have to pretend with old Dad.
告诉我 是谁那么幸运
Go on, tell me, who's the lucky fella?
哎哟 Daria 我希望他没有逼你做... 一些事
Gee, Daria, I hope he's not pressuring you to, uh, do... anything.
好吧 被你猜对了
All right, you figured me out.
他是我学长 他会往手臂上刻字
He's a senior and he carves words into his arm.
我们希望可以一起克服青少年婚姻的艰难险阻
Together we're hoping to buck the odds against teen marriages.
真会说笑啊 Daria
That's a good one, Daria.
我在开玩笑
I'm kidding.
当然啊 小鬼 我知道
Of course you are, kiddo. I knew that.
噢 如果有个叫Knuckles的打电话来 是找我的
Oh. If someone named Knuckles calls, it's for me.
Daria 才回家呀
Daria, just getting home?
我要补体育课
I had to make up gym.
真的吗 为什么
Really? Why?
老师上课在搞啦啦操排练 我坐一边没搭理
The teacher was running a cheerleading practice during class, so I sat out.
我才不要跟白痴一样上蹿下跳 来向这个我不相信的世界证明
I'm not going to jump up and down like an idiot to prove to the world what I don't believe,
做运动员很棒这件事
which is that jocks are great.
挺好的 亲爱的
Good for you, honey.
唯一扭转这个男人主导世界的方法
The only way it will stop being a man's world is
就是让他们也穿着热裤大跳啦啦操
if we get the boys out there in their short shorts cheering, too.
我是说 双重标准气数该尽了 对吧 Jake
What I mean is, this double standard has got to end, right, Jake?
同工同酬
Equal pay for equal work.
是吧
Is that right?
Daria 我不赞同你拒绝参与班级活动
Daria, I don't approve of refusing to participate in class,
但是我的女儿也绝不能陷入
but no daughter of mine is going to buy into the mindset
"女人的人生目标就是取悦男人"的思维模式
that a woman's purpose in life is pleasing men.
我的新鞋好看吗
Like my new shoes?
把我脚趾都夹起泡了 但也让我的双腿看上去无比火辣
They pinch my toes and give me blisters but they make my legs look hot
所以我还要再买一双
so I'm going to buy another pair.
所以Helen支持你在体育课上的举动?
So Helen actually supported you on this gym class thing?
她残存的是非观又出来逞能了
Her vestigial sense of right and wrong was acting up again.
你妈怎么看
What does your mother think about it?
我不知道
I don't know.
等她从彩色沙漠回来之后 我会问问她的
When she gets back from the painted desert I'll ask her if she had a vision.
*佩恩蒂德沙漠（美国亚利桑那州中北部的沙漠）
你知道的 我真的想向Morris老师证明
You know, I'd really like to show that Ms. Morris
Lane不是什么一般的废柴
that the Lanes are no bunch of ordinary deadbeats.
当然不是了
Of course not.
你是有范儿的废柴
You're deadbeats with style.
没错 不过说到范儿 群魔乱舞的潮女出现了
Exactly, and speaking of style: fashion fiends at high noon.
你们想象一下去参加个体育运动
Can you imagine joining an actual sport?
你会一身臭汗 妆也要花了
You'd get all sweaty and your makeup would smudge.
女生该去钓运动员 而不是成为运动员
You're supposed to date jocks, not be one.
我在Waif杂志上看到说跑步会让脚大一号
Oh, and I read in Waif that running makes your feet spread to a bigger shoe size,
看起来会非常 非常丑
which would look really, really, really bad.
穿着这双鞋脚感如何 Quinn
How are your feet in those new shoes, Quinn?
快挤死我了
They're killing me.
噢 太糟糕了
Oh... that's too bad.
什么样的衰货才会报名田径队啊
What kind of loser would sign up for the track team?
你们不会觉得我也衰吧
You girls don't think I'm a loser, do you?
你是想约我们出去玩吗
Are you asking if you can hang out with us?
不是
Nope.
我喜欢对健身态度开明一些的女生
I prefer women with a slightly more enlightened attitude toward fitness.
哦是吗
Oh, yeah?
还真存在有着五零后的旧思维的八零后啊
I guess you can be born in the '80s and still stuck in the '50s.
真是难以相信现在还有活人
It's hard to believe there's anyone alive
觉得运动员就不算淑女了
who still thinks being athletic isn't ladylike.
只要努力 女性可以在各类体育项目里出类拔萃
Women can excel at any sport they put their minds to.
我完全同意
I definitely agree with that.
我也是 我要报名田径队
Me, too. I'd like to sign up for the track team.
啥
What?
Lane 你在这做什么
Miss Lane, what are you doing here?
田径队考核
Trying out for track team.
你连普通的体育课都不去上
You won't participate in regular gym class,
现在倒想参与课外运动了?
but you want to join an extracurricular sport?
我喜欢跑步
I like to run.
好吧 那就来看看你会不会跑
Okay. Let's see if you're any good at it.
我尤其喜欢穿着钉鞋在你的脊椎上跑来跑去
I'd particularly like to run up and down your spine wearing track spikes.
你不喜欢这个老师吗
She isn't your favorite teacher?
我们有笔帐没算
We have a score to settle.
顺便 我是Evan
I'm Evan, by the way.
Jane
Jane.
你准备好加入田径队了?
So, you think you're ready for track?
对啊 要是队员都是烂人的话我戴上耳机就好
Yeah. I figure if the people suck I can always wear headphones.
我比你领先一大步
I'm way ahead of you.
比了再说
Until we get out there.
你走回去吗
You walking home?
嗯今天不行 要训练
Um, not today. Practice.
你成功加入田径队了？
So you made the track team?
是的
Yeah.
这种时候你该说
This is the part where you say,
"嘿 好样的 可喜可贺"
"Hey, way to go, congratulations."
嘿 好样的
Hey, way to go.
可喜可贺呢?
Congratulations...?
可喜可贺
Congratulations.
别对我这么腻腻歪歪的
Now, don't get mushy on me.
请锁定呕心小世界
Next, on Sick, Sad World.
Jane 参加了校队 真是可悲
Jane. On a school team. That's pathetic.
等等 如果她算可悲 那我跟自己说话又算什么
Hey, if she's the pathetic one, why am I talking to myself?
更重要的是 为什么我在等她的回复
And more importantly, why am I waiting for a reply?
Quinn 你真是太棒了
Quinn, it is so great of you
可以请我们一起过来看地球小姐选美
to invite us over to watch the Miss Continents of the Earth Pageant.
噢 Sandi 你能来也真是太棒了
Oh, Sandi, it's so great of you to come over.
Quinn 你那个远房亲戚也赖在你家太久了吧
Quinn, your cousin or whatever sure spends a lot of time at your house.
是啊 呃 她没别的地方可去了
Yes, well, um, she has nowhere else to go,
谁让她父母都坐牢了
what with her parents being in jail and all.
快看 开始了
Look, it's starting.
你们现在不该穿着睡衣
Shouldn't you all be running around in teddies
互相给对方打扮吗?
and giving each other makeovers by now?
她穿芥色丑爆了
Mustard is not her color.
噢 无盐无油脱脂的爆米花好了
Oh, the no-salt, no-oil, fat-free popcorn is ready.
爆米花?
Popcorn?
别说了 我要流口水了
Stop, my mouth is watering.
是哟 我也喜欢穿泳衣的时候配高跟鞋呢
Oh, yeah, I know I like to wear heels with my bathing suit.
而且我去游泳一定要画唇线呢
And I never go swimming without my lip liner.
Quinn 有件事要问你
Quinn, I need to ask you something.
好吧 周二晚上我没有帮联合劝募会洗车 但是 妈
All right, so Tuesday night I wasn't washing cars for the United Way, but Mom,
如果你看到他那么帅气的笑 你就会懂的
if you'd seen his boyish smile you'd understand.
事实上 我是想让你多花点时间陪陪你姐
Actually, I wanted to ask you to spend some time with your sister.
你干嘛不把我丢阁楼里锁到25岁?
Why don't you just lock me in the attic till I'm 25?
我不能再为她牺牲了 妈 我不能了
I can't sacrifice any more for her, Mother, I just can't.
Quinn 我很担心
Quinn, I'm worried.
她独处的时间太长了 我觉得她会自言自语
She's alone too much and I think she's talking to herself.
就陪她一下午吧 她也会愿意为你这么做的
Just give her an afternoon. She'd do it for you.
如果要我答应这桩苦差事的话
Should I agree to perform this sensitive and difficult task,
我还没说要答应啊 好处是什么
and I'm not saying I will, what's in it for me?
我很失望你会这么问 但是
I am disappointed that it's come to this, but...
我的信用卡给你去逛商场
you can take my credit card to the mall.
- 白金卡？－绿卡
- Platinum? - Green.
－金卡－成交
- Gold. - Done.
有人敲门 请进
Someone's knocking. Come in.
嗨 Daria 还好吗
Hi, Daria, how's it going?
有事说事
Okay. Out with it.
我在想咱们是不是...
I was thinking that you and I could...
能一起玩一会儿
you know, do something together.
好吧 你是谁 你把Quinn藏哪去了
All right, who are you, and where are you hiding Quinn?
- 啥? 妹妹就不能花时间和她... - 远房亲戚?
- What? Can't a sister spend time with her... - Cousin?
好吧 妈妈逼我来跟你待一会
All right, Mom is forcing me to hang out with you.
逼?
Forcing?
我拿了她的金卡
I've got her gold card.
你干嘛不早说
Why didn't you say so?
让我领第一笔款 你就可以跟我去图书馆了
Give me the first cash advance and you can come with me to the library.
图书馆? 要是被谁看见了我就死定了
The library? If anyone saw me there, I'd die.
好吧 那商场怎么样
Okay, then, how about the mall?
你朋友们混的地方
You know, where your friends hang out.
嗨
Um, hi.
可以给我们念本书吗
Will you read to me?
我很喜欢听故事
I really like stories.
你不用跟我讲故事 只要说话就行
You don't have to tell me a story. Just talk.
Jack和Jill爬上了山之类的鬼地方 到了样品展销会
So Jack and Jill went up the hill or whatever to the sample sale,
Jill看中了一身完美的套装
where Jill found the perfect ensemble
Jack把这作为纪念交往一个月的礼物送给了她
and Jack gave it to her for the one-month anniversary of their first date.
嗨 Quinn
Hey, Quinn.
我来这接我弟弟回去
I just came by to pick up my little brother from story hour.
我不知道你也喜欢看书呢
I didn't know you were a reader.
嗨 Calvin 我其实不...
Hi, Calvin. I'm not actually...
真是太赞了
That's really cool.
我是说 你这么受欢迎 没必要做义工的
I mean, you're popular; you don't have to volunteer.
噢 你知道的啦 回报总比付出多嘛
Oh, well, you know, I get back more than I give.
我是说 孩子们很喜欢这样
I mean, the children appreciate it so.
呃 管理员
Uh, librarian...
可以帮我把这些杂志放回去吗
could you return these magazines for me?
多谢了 亲爱的
Thanks a bunch, dear.
那 你们现在去哪儿呢
So, where are you guys headed now?
"纤纤细腿送给你的那个他"
"Thin Thighs For Your Man."
可我不喜欢男人纤纤细腿
But I don't like men with thin thighs.
拿下那个运动鞋代言了吗
Land that big sneaker endorsement yet?
没 他们接受不了我开的价
Nah, they wouldn't meet my price.
今天是我们第一次运动会
Today's our first track meet.
我不介意你去看比赛
I wouldn't mind if you were there.
嗯 我实在是不想翘掉我的线形舞课...
Oh. Well, you know how I hate to cancel my line-dancing lesson...
不过好吧
but okay.
好
Cool.
关键是 我是在支持朋友还是支持她屈服于体制的行为?
The question is, am I supporting my friend or her surrender to the system?
走开可以吗 这是私人谈话
Do you mind? This is a private conversation.
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
Trent 你在这儿干嘛
Trent? What are you doing here?
我来给Jane助威
I came to support Janey.
他们又在给我的房间大扫除
They're power-scrubbing my room again.
总之 跑步这事儿对她意义重大
Anyway, this running stuff means lot to her.
她做的事儿需要勇气
What she's doing takes guts.
那么多训练 日复一日
All that practicing, day in, day out.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿 Jane还不赖嘛
Hey, Jane's good.
她好棒啊
She's great!
加油 加油 冲
Go, go, kick butt.
你训练的时候真是错过了太多好节目
And you missed a lot of really good TV while you were at those practices.
那天有个特别节目 说的是怀恨在心的动物
The other day, they had this special, When Animals Hold a Grudge.
Jane 你太惊艳了 第一名啊
Jane, you were amazing. First place?
是啊 祝贺祝贺
Yeah, congratulations.
谢了 我只是假装自己在逃开动员大会而已
Thanks, I just pretend I'm running away from a pep rally.
哟 哥们
Yo, bro!
该走了
Gotta go.
反正就是有只小鹦鹉因为主人没给他换水 真的气...
So anyway, this one parakeet was really ticked off at its owner for not changing its water...
嗨 队友 你看见那个风一般的女子了吗
Hey, teammate. Did you see this girl run like the wind?
你听过她放屁吗
Have you ever heard her break wind?
Daria
Daria!
好逗啊
That's pretty funny.
训练见了 小旋风
See you at practice, speedy.
总之那个小鹦鹉一直等到他的主...
So anyway, the parakeet waits until its owner...
Daria 你刚才到底是几个意思
Jeez, Daria, what the hell was that about?
什么
What?
嘿 嘿 嘿 田径之星啊
Hey, hey, hey, it's the track star.
你会享受运动员生活的 姐们
You're gonna like being a jock, man.
一旦成了人生赢家 人人都想跟你做朋友
When you're a winner, everybody wants to be your friend.
那些人跟你原来那个无聊的朋友可不一样
Not like those boring friends you used to have
她在你迷茫的时候都还守着你呢
who liked you even when you lost.
你是说那个拿我无下限开涮的朋友吗
You mean the ones who made incredibly humiliating jokes at my expense?
够了吧你
Oh, come on.
是你够了 Daria
You come on, Daria.
我尝试了新事物
So, I tried something different.
我冒了险 我配合了 功夫不负有心人
I went out on a limb and participated in something and it worked out.
你生哪门子的气啊
Why do you have to be so pissy about it?
呃 北鼻 这怪尴尬的是吧
Uh, babe, this is really awkward, right?
是啊北鼻
Yeah, babe.
吓到我了
It's creeping me out!
噢 Kevvy 来吧
Oh, Kevvy, come on.
Brittany小护士来治愈你
Nurse Brittany gonna make you feel all better.
好吧 我以为我只是在开玩笑
All right, so I thought I was making a joke,
结果是在你喜欢的男生面前羞辱了你
but I was really humiliating you in front of this guy you like...
是欣赏
Appreciate.
你欣赏的男生 是我蠢是我反应迟钝
This guy you appreciate, which was stupid and insensitive.
我是白痴 对不起 行了吧
So I'm an idiot and I'm sorry. Okay?
等等
Not so fast.
我怎么知道你是诚心诚意
How do I know this is a sincere apology
还是只想让我消气随便使的花招
and not a cheap ploy to get back on my good side?
这两者有区别吗
Why does there have to be a difference?
我接受道歉
I accept.
谢了 放学一起吃披萨
Thank you. Pizza after school?
我也想 要训练
Wish I could. Practice.
为了防止再被留堂 我们还是跟着一起跳吧
I guess we'd better join the rest of the cheerleaders before we get detention again.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
什么意思
What do you mean?
Jane 你的腿怎么样了
How are the legs, Jane?
还好 比赛完有点酸
Okay. Maybe a little sore after the meet.
酸? 那你最好休息一下
Sore? You better rest up for tomorrow.
来 去我办公室看电视
Here, go watch TV in my office.
这个嘛
I don't know.
我不是很想一个人去
I-I don't really want to be all by myself...
Morgendorffer 你跟她一起去
Ms. Morgendorffer, you join her.
遵命 长官 一切为了队伍 长官
Yes, ma'am. Anything for the team, ma'am.
她可是你的死对头啊
So that's your archenemy.
你觉得我从我鄙视的女人身上捞好处虚伪吗?
You think it's hypocritical of me to accept favors from a woman I despise?
她那能看有线节目吗
Does she have cable?
去了就知道
Let's find out.
噢 他们在吃晚饭
Oh, they're eating dinner.
我要坐下来一起还是假装头痛呢
Should I sit down and join them or fake a headache?
我不太舒服
I'm not feeling too well.
我待会再吃
I think I'll eat later.
噢天哪 她又抽风了
Oh, boy, cuckoo girl is at it again.
我真的很担心 她这样已经好几天了
I'm really worried. She's been acting this way for days.
都怪那个叫Knuckles的
It's that guy, Knuckles!
我告诉你 他把我们女儿搞蒙了
I tell you, he's messing with her head!
Quinn 你不是要跟你姐姐多相处一会吗
Quinn, I thought you were going to spend some time with your sister.
噢是啊 看
Oh, yeah, here.
这是什么
What's this?
这是我的时间表 上面写明了
Well, that one is my time sheet showing the hours
我在何时何地照顾了Daria
and locations where I baby-sat Daria.
还有一张是我新买的皮夹克的收据 谢啦
And that other one is a receipt for my new pleather jacket. Thanks.
300刀
$300?!
爸 要逗她开心好难的
Dad, it's very difficult to keep her amused.
噢 如果清单上有出现提现记录的话
Oh, and when the cash advance shows up on the statement?
别怪我 是Daria干的
Don't blame me, that's Daria's.
数学考试怎么样
How'd the math test go?
我过了
I passed.
你倒是想
You hope.
是啊
I know.
真是自信啊
Well, aren't we confident.
如果我有这...
If I had as much trouble wi...
你免考了 是不是
You got a bye on the test, didn't you?
我可能还是只能拿个C
I probably would have gotten a "C" anyway.
难以置信
I can't believe it!
喂 你可是没上体育课跟我一起看电视了的
Hey, you watched TV with me instead of going to gym.
所以呢
So?
所以那就算是加入长跑队的一个好处
So, that was one perk of being on the team.
数学考试是另一个
The math test was another.
你不觉得这两者有区别吗
You don't see any difference?
是啊 数学考试这个好处大多了
Yeah, the math test was a of a lot better.
拉倒吧你
Give me a break.
你朋友怎么了
What's up with your friend?
噢 我伤害了她的伪善
Oh, I rubbed her self-righteousness the wrong way.
总之啊 我不知道你干嘛还和她一起玩
I don't know why you hang out with her anyway.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
嗯 你现在算是体育明星了
Well, you're sort of a sports star now.
跟... 衰货一起玩可不怎么酷噢
It's not so cool to be hanging around with... you know, losers.
是啊 你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
我真是在衰货们身上花了太多时间了
I've been spending too much time with losers.
我很高兴... 你懂我的意思
I'm glad you... see it my way.
承认吧 她说的有道理
Admit it, she had a point.
我都沾光了 怎么还有资格来批评她
Who am I to criticize her when I was getting spillover perks?
天呐 我真希望她能退了那个破队
God, I wish she'd just quit that damn team.
让我也堕落了
It's corrupting me.
我来开
I'll get it.
是我
Yo, it's me.
表现得自然点 你没有受伤
Act natural. You're not hurt.
什么
What?
听着 我一直在想... 你说得对
Look, I've been thinking and... you're right.
我免考的行为真是太堕落了
It was really screwed up of me to take a bye on that math test.
我应该亲赴考场 光荣牺牲才对
I should have gone in there and failed it on my own.
他们给了你机会走捷径
They gave you the chance to cut a corner.
你接受了我也不能怪你
I can't blame you for taking it.
这都是因为我想向Morris老师证明我不是游手好闲的人
This all happened because I was trying to prove to Ms. Morris that I'm not a deadbeat.
还有那个叫Evan的也搀和进来了
And that Evan guy factors in exactly how?
那个混蛋? 我不敢相信你还觉得他不错
That jerk? I can't believe you thought he was cute.
是啊 我真是笨啊
Yeah. Aren't I a dope?
诶 你不用去训练吗
Hey, don't you have practice now?
不用 我退了
Yeah. I quit.
什么
What?
我退了
I quit.
我怕高中毕业后变得跟Kevin懂得一样多
I'm afraid I might come out of high school knowing as much as Kevin.
你幼儿园毕业就比Kevin懂得多了
You came out of kindergarten knowing more than Kevin.
倒是让我想起了他拿橄榄球奖学金的事
Remind me of that when he gets his football scholarship.
我保证 明天就把钉鞋带回来
I'll bring the spikes back tomorrow. Honest.
Jane 我希望你可以考虑归队
Jane, I wish you would consider coming back to the team.
谢了 不过我坚持自己的决定
Thanks, but I stand by my decision.
Jane 我希望你可以考虑归队
Jane, I wish you would consider coming back to the team.
我错过什么了吗
Am I missing something?
这个队需要你 你也需要这个队
The team needs you, and you need the team...
如果你这个夏天不想再参加数学考试的话
if you don't want to be here taking math again this summer.
哟 听上去跟敲诈似的
Gee, that almost sounds like blackmail.
幸运的是 我可以自己提高数学成绩
Fortunately, I can pull up my math grade on my own.
那我就要让你挂
Then I'll flunk you.
我不如去找Li老师披露这种成绩交换的勾当吧?
Why don't I go to Ms. Li and expose this grade-changing arrangement?
她已经知道了
She already knows.
好吧 你闪开 不然我就报告家长教师联谊会
Okay, then, back off or I'll tell the P.T.A.
他们也知道了
They know, too.
国会呢
Congress?
你输定了 Lane
You're beaten, Lane.
那我打电话给三个本地电视台
How about if I call the three local TV stations
再告诉每一家 其他两家在跟这个报道?
and tell each one that the other two are running the story?
该死
Damn.
我真的不懂你
I really don't get you.
你确实不懂
No. You don't.
你那双性感惹火的高跟鞋呢
What happened to your come-and-get-it heels?
哈哈 Daria
Ha-ha, Daria.
我决定不穿那双要我命的鞋了
I decided I shouldn't wear shoes that kill me
尽管他们让我的双腿看上去万分惹火
just because they make my legs look hot.
为什么 Quinn 多成熟啊
Why, Quinn, how mature.
我是说 我的腿无论穿什么都那么性感
I mean, my legs look hot no matter what I wear.
哪怕穿你身上的那些玩意也一样
They'd probably even look good in those things you have on.
我觉得事情已经不能更悲催了
I didn't think things could get any more pathetic,
但是很明显我错了
but obviously I was wrong.
动起来 姑娘们
Come on, ladies.
你们还有一大截要追上呢
You've got a lot of work to make up.
告诉我 至少我的节操还在
Tell me that at least I have my integrity.
节操真是个有意思的词
Integrity is a funny word.
那至少告诉我 我还没有那些运动员那么堕落
Well, then, at least tell me I'm marginally less corrupt than the jocks.
你拒绝配合这个扭曲的体制
You refused to participate in a crooked system
在这个体制里体育特长可以换来好的分数
where good grades are exchanged for athletic performance.
但是你也没有改良这个体制
But you didn't try to reform the system, either.
因为害怕完全边缘化
For fear of complete teenage exile.
没错
Right.
所以这个体制还是运作着 你也没能救赎自己
So the system continues, you haven't redeemed yourself,
我们也依然被排斥着
and we're ostracized anyway.
够了吧你 别描绘什么光明的图景了
Come on, now, stop trying to paint a rosy picture.
你知道吗
You know what?
什么
What?
他们真的在帮我们接受现实世界
They really are preparing us for the real world.
Daria Jane 快来啊 是时候劈叉了
Daria! Jane! Come on! It's time for splits!
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组